{
  "ids": 5,
  "question_db_by_id": {
    "0": {
      "subject": "anglais",
      "type": "qcm",
      "level": "facile",
      "question": "Traduire \"Haut\"",
      "answer": "High"
    },
    "1": {
      "subject": "math",
      "type": "courte",
      "level": "difficile",
      "question": "1+1",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    "2": {
      "subject": "francais",
      "type": "longue",
      "level": "moyen",
      "question": "Corrigez les fautes : Les fleur son belle",
      "answer": "Les fleurs sont belles"
    },
    "3": {
      "subject": "math",
      "type": "courte",
      "level": "facile",
      "question": "25+12",
      "answer": "37"
    },
    "4": {
      "subject": "anglais",
      "type": "courte",
      "level": "difficile",
      "question": "Traduire \"Ordinateur\"",
      "answer": "Computer"
    }
  },
  "question_db_by_sub": {
    "anglais": {
      "0": {
      "subject": "anglais",
      "type": "qcm",
      "level": "facile",
      "question": "Traduire \"Haut\"",
      "answer": "High"
    },
      "4": {
      "subject": "anglais",
      "type": "courte",
      "level": "difficile",
      "question": "Traduire \"Ordinateur\"",
      "answer": "Computer"
      }
    },
    "math": {
      "1": {
      "subject": "math",
      "type": "courte",
      "level": "difficile",
      "question": "1+1",
      "answer": "2"
    },
      "3": {
      "subject": "math",
      "type": "courte",
      "level": "facile",
      "question": "25+12",
      "answer": "37"
      }
    },
    "2": {
      "subject": "francais",
      "type": "longue",
      "level": "moyen",
      "question": "Corrigez les fautes : Les fleur son belle",
      "answer": "Les fleurs sont belles"
      }
    }
  }
}